{
    "quiz": [
        {
            "question": "When Harry used a magic firstly?",
            "answers": ["In dream", "In zoo", "In the car"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did Harry get the letter from Hogwarts?",
            "answers": ["On the lighthouse", "At home", "In the car"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the core of Harry's wand?",
            "answers": ["From a unicorn", "From a fenix", "From a dragon heart"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was on Harry's first card from the box of chocolate frogs?",
            "answers": ["Snape", "Dumbledore", "Volandemort"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did Harry first meet Draco Malfoy?",
            "answers": ["In the train", "In Hogwarts", "In a crooked alley"],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question":"What kind of dragon did Hagrid have?",
            "answers":["Hungarian Horntail","Norwegian humpback dragon","Ukrainian iron-bellied dragon"],
            "correct":2
        },
        {
            "question":"In the battle with which creature did Harry and Ron help Hermione?",
            "answers":["Pixie","Troll","Dragon", "Unicorn"],
            "correct":2
        },
        {
            "question":"What instrument was used to put the three-headed dog to sleep?",
            "answers":["A violin","A flute","A harp"],
            "correct":3
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the make of the Weasley family car?",
            "answers":["Ford","BMW","Audi","Volkswagen"],
            "correct":1
        },
        {
            "question":"How many secret passages are there from Hogwarts?",
            "answers":["7","3","11","22"],
            "correct":1
        },
        {
            "question":"How many deathly gifts are there?",
            "answers":["2","4","1","3"],
            "correct":4
        }
    ]
}